Typhoon No. 2 continues
to grow and is moving north,
causing unstable weather conditions
in the Kanto and Tohoku regions.
SUBJECT: TYPHOON NO. 2 APPROACHING
YOU ARE ENCOURAGED TO WORK FROM HOME TODAY.
At this time, the typhoon is still generating
strong winds, but is expected to weaken.
There is a possibility that the typhoon
will approach the Kanto region again
TYPHOON NO. 2
between tonight and tomorrow morning.
It's moving quickly, and the wind
and rain may suddenly strengthen.
Please avoid unnecessary outings,
and regularly check recent updates.
They're tellin' us to stay home,
there are some things I can't
do unless I'm at the office.
I gotta take samples to
the meeting place, too...
Wait. It's one thing for me,
but what about Kamegawa?
As a mentor, am I s'posed to allow
the newbie to show up to work
when a typhoon is comin'?
But Kamegawa needs to
attend the meeting, too...
And there's that deadline
for the sunscreen proposal...
This ain't the time for me to daydream!
Rainy weather pumps: check!
Towel in bag: check!
Today, I'm gonna finish work early
so I can send Kamegawa home!
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
EPISODE 5: IT'S ALL THE TYPHOON'S FAULT
"It's All the Typhoon's Fault!"
Is everyone working remotely?
Then that means...
Good morning.
M-Morning...
I'm alone with Kamegawa...
The wind's really strong today!
Looks like everyone is working from home.
Let's finish our work early before the
typhoon keeps us from getting home.
Yes, ma'am!
Normally, this place is bustlin',
but today it's just the two of us.
I'm gettin' a li'l nervous.
No, I should be used to
being with Kamegawa by now!
The two of us even had to share a room
during the Okinawa business trip...
Wait. Now that I think about it,
that situation could have been avoided.
Gotta focus on my work!
It's really raining now.
I was hoping we could leave
while the weather was okay.
It couldn't be helped.
Are your shoes waterproof?
Oh, these are the ones I always wear.
Could it be that your shoes
are okay in the rain, Senpai?
Yeah.
I didn't know there were cute
rain boots like those.
What kind of person would wear
normal shoes during weather like this?
Business-style rain shoes exist,
so be prepared next time.
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
It's raining cats and dogs.
The forecast did say that the
typhoon was moving quickly.
I forgot my umbrella...
What?!
What is this? I gave Kamegawa
a talkin'-to about shoes,
but I'm the one who forgot an umbrella!
Rain means bring an umbrella! An umbrella!
I'm going to a convenience store,
so you go on ahe—
Please use mine, if you'd like.
Huh?
But then you'll get wet!
I always keep a collapsible
umbrella in my bag.
Not only did he bring an umbrella,
but he keeps a spare on hand, too?
The wind's real strong...
You doing okay?!
Yes, somehow...
Th-Thank y—
Use this umbrella instead!
What? No, I'm good!
You should use it, Senpai.
It's your umbrella!
I'll borrow that one instead—
It's okay!
I can still use this one.
If you show up drenched to the meeting,
it'll only bother the others.
Oh! Y-You're right!
I'll hold it, then.
Let's go!
Yeah.
He's...
so close!
Are you getting wet, Senpai?
I-I'm okay.
Keep your eyes forward.
Yes, ma'am!
Was he always this tall?
Since he's closer, he feels even more...
This ain't the time to think like this!
Thank you for coming
despite the awful weather.
No, thank you for having us.
We wanted you to see the
finalized collab items directly.
Thank you!
I'll have Kamegawa give you the details.
Thank you for having me.
RACING GIRLS COLLAB CAFÉ
Referencing the new tracks that are
scheduled to release in the next update,
5 TYPES OF PARFAITS
we're thinking of preparing
five different parfaits.
COLLAB GOODS
These were designed in collaboration with the maid café we will be working with...
This newbie's good at his job, as always.
In comparison, I forgot my umbrella
and he had to lend me one...
I at least need to achieve my goal
of sending him home early!
Even with our umbrellas,
we can't avoid getting wet.
Kamegawa.
Yes?
Hold still.
S-Sorry. Thank you.
This reminds me of my cat at my parent's place.
Take off your jacket and dry it.
Okay.
Are you okay with a latte?
Yeah.
I'll go get that for you.
It'll get all wrinkly if he hangs it like that.
How does one hang this kind of suit?
Wow, it's huge.
Flap, flap, flap...
Um...
Thanks...
Looks like it's going to hit Kanto
sooner than expected.
Something the matter?
Huh?
Ah, no.
I was just thinking about
how heavy the rain is.
Are you perhaps... a bit excited about this?
Huh?
Stare...
Sorry, I'm being imprudent, aren't I?
It's just so unusual.
I can't help but feel a little restless.
The longer you work,
the less you'll say stuff like that.
You're still a child.
B-But then what does that make you?
You were just playing with my suit.
A-Are you all right?!
There are times I wanna
be childish, too, y'know!
That one sounded really close.
Calm down, calm down.
Y-You're right.
Sorry—
This is a business district,
so the lightning should
hit a lightning rod...
Y-You're right. Yeah.
Let's play shiritori!
Ringo (apple).
Gomi (trash).
Mikan (mandarin)... oops...
You're the one who suggested the game...
The lightning's stopped now.
Okay. Let's get back to work.
Yes, ma'am!
You can head home first, Kamegawa.
What? But I still have work...
What you've gotten done is enough.
Go home before the trains stop running.
But you're going to stay, right?
I'll have to work from home tomorrow, so...
I need to finish what I can only do
in the office now while I still can.
Um, is there anything I can do to help?
No, I'm all right.
You can assign me anything, Senpai.
Then...
Sorry to ask, but could you go get the
documents from Sales before they leave?
Roger.
I'm going to attend an online meeting now.
Just leave the documents on my desk.
You can go home after that.
Yes, ma'am.
How is he such a kind creature?
Excuse me, can I have a moment?
Coming.
Huh? Kamegawa?!
Tsukahara-senpai!
It's been a while!
SALES DEPARTMENT - SHUN TSUKAHARA
What're you doing, coming in on a day like this?
They're working the rookie to the bone!
Not at all.
What about you, Senpai?
You're not working from home today?
Yeah, the payment deadline is crazy today.
I could really use a helping hand right now.
That concludes today's meeting.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
Excuse us.
Thank you very much.
Good work today.
Thank you for your continued support.
YOU HAVE LEFT THE MEETING
I managed to finish my work.
Are the trains even runnin' now?
I'm glad I was at least able to
send Kamegawa home early.
Good work today!
You're—
What are you doing?! Why are you here?!
What if the last train's already left?!
I thought I said you could head home...
No, I definitely said that!
I'm sorry, I—
Hurry and pack up. We're going home.
I'm going to stay a bit longer.
What's that?!
I was asked to help out a bit.
Asked? By who?
Tsukahara-san from Sales.
He helped me out back
when I was job searching.
He said he could use my help
if I happened to be free, so...
Senpai?
Hey!
Kannawa...
And Kamegawa?
What brings you two here?
I'm Kamegawa's mentor.
Oh, I see.
And?
Was there something wrong
with the documents I just gave you?
Could you please refrain from pushing
work onto someone else's subordinate?
Huh?
Wait, I only asked if he happened
to be free... Right?
If you can't do it, that's fine.
I didn't force it on him or anything.
Being "asked" by a senior
is the same as "forcing."
You know that, and that's
why you asked him.
Kamegawa's saying that he's going to
work overtime because of your work.
Do your own job.
I won't tolerate my precious junior
working overtime on a day like this!
My bad.
Oh, no worries!
Excuse me.
Um...
Thank you.
Just tell him "no" next time.
Yes, ma'am.
Are the trains still running?
Looks like just barely, yes.
Th-Then let's head to the station.
I-It's okay.
In weather like this, it makes no difference
whether you have an umbrella or not.
Senpai!
Would you like to share an umbrella
until we reach the station?
N-No... The station's right there,
so we can just run—
It's not safe!
The wind's pretty strong.
If something were to hit you...
I may not be that useful on the job yet,
but I believe I can be of use
in times like these.
I may be your junior, but I'm also a man.
Wait, that came out weird.
I meant I have a man's strength!
Strength!
R-Right.
Shall we go?
Uh-huh.
Are you okay?
A junior, but also a man...
I knew that, but...
You were right, Senpai.
I don't think the umbrella's helping.
No, it's helping!
Back then...
I was just panicking.
S-Sorry, I just...
It's okay.
Hey!
You don't need to lean that
toward me so much. You'll get wet.
But...
Then could you please lean more toward me?
Huh?
I-Isn't it hard to walk?
I'm okay!
Thank you for using the train system.
I didn't know we took the same train.
We will soon arrive at Akabane. Akabane.
Me neither.
You always stayed longer at
the office, so I had no idea.
Please make sure you have
all of your belongings.
The doors on the right side will open.
We sure got wet.
The next station is Akabane, JA15.
It was raining buckets, after all.
The doors on the right side will open.
Please change here for the Keihin-Tohoku Line, the Utsunomiya Line,
Thanks for your help today. With everything.
the Takasaki Line, and the Ueno-Tokyo Line.
No way. I should be the one thanking you.
Oh. This is my stop.
Senpai!
Please take this, if you'd like.
Huh?
I live close to the station, so...
It's okay if it breaks, too.
Th-Then... here.
It's better than nothing.
Thank you.
The train on track 8 is now departing.
I'll see you tomorrow, then.
Please stand clear of the closing doors.
Oh, wait, it'll be remote.
Good work, anyway!
Good work today!
I'm so glad we work from home tomorrow.
I wouldn't know how to face him...
Should I buy some
nice-smelling fabric softener?